Daniel Romero

Front End Developer

Daniel Romero

13420 Doty Ave Apt 14 Hawthorne, CA 90250

714.679.6375

danny@dannys.io | dannyk08@github | dannyk08@linkedin

Summary

Three years developing and maintaining web applications using modern frameworks and practices. I am looking for a Front End Developer role at an organization where there's a large emphasis on mentorship, growth, and building maintainable applications with modern tools.

Experience

ForceField / Mobile Developer

November 2017 - December 2017, Los Angeles

Contributed as a contractor to improve offline mobile experience for ForceField's Child Android application.

Winc (Formerly ClubW) / Front End Developer

June 2015 - October 2017, Los Angeles

Maintained and updated Winc's internal administrative system used for managing membership accounts and warehouse inventory. Reduced incidence of bugs and streamlined internal workflows.

Partnered with internal teams to create new features like FedEx hold location integration, a tag based search engine, image uploader and cropper, dynamic partnership on our products detail page.

Established specifications and developed a customizable landing page generator and content management system. Empowered the marketing team to create their own customized landing pages, greatly reducing the time and engineering resources needed to launch new marketing campaigns.

Education

General Assembly / Full Stack Web Development Immersive

November 2014 - February 2015, Santa Monica

Golden West College / A.A.S in Biology & A.A. in General Science

August 2008 - August 2014, Huntington Beach

Notable Skills

2017 - Angular 4, Webpack 2, AWS S3, React, React Native, Redux, Jest, VueJS, Vuex

2016 - Angular 1 & 2, NodeJS, ExpressJS, Typescript, Coffeescript, GruntJS, GulpJS, RethinkDB, Material UI, EJS

2015 - Jade, Foundation 5, HTML5, SASS, CSS3, jQuery